[Music]
we all share the same
destination we all work together as
one in this place there's only one
vision and that's to be the number
number
one we all have the right
combination care and quality there's no
[Music]
compromise doing the very best will be
our
mission it's something that we need to
realize it's something very special in
our
eyes we are poal
our values means a lot we are the
people who Give It All We L with a sunny
disposition we can overcome the loss yes
we have a valid reason to
believe we are number
one take one more
step reach out for
Excellence we'll do whatever it takes to
touch the
sky and we'll help each other reach our
aspirations we know that we can do it if
we
[Music]
strive we are
credential our bance means a l Beyond
people who Give It All We Got
with a sun
disposition we can overcome the AR yes
we have a valid reason
[Music]
to we are number
one we are number
one we are number one